(Amy:)Now let's talk about Priya,
that man-stealing bitch.
(Bernadette:)What?
(Amy:)In situations like this,
(Amy:)best girlfriends are often
catty about the other woman.
(Penny:)Really, I am not upset
about Leonard and Priya.
(Amy:)Oh. Then perhaps you don't
understand what's going on.
(Amy:)Your former boyfriend
has replaced you
(Amy:)with what appears to be
a very suitable mate.
(Amy:)Arguably much
more suitable than you.
(Penny:)Oh. Well, good for him.
(Penny:)Hey, what do you mean,
"more suitable"?
(Amy:)Well, granted, Penny, your
secondary sexual characteristics
(Amy:)are reasonably bodacious.
(Amy:)But Priya is highly educated,
(Amy:)she's an accomplished
professional,
(Amy:)and she comes from the culture
that literally wrote the book
(Amy:)on neat ways to have sex.
(Amy:)Whereas you, on the other hand,
are a community college dropout
(Amy:)who comes from the culture that
wrote the book on tipping cows.
(Penny:)Yeah. Okay, I got it.
(Penny:)I got it.
(Penny:)So... what is
all that stuff?